About two and half years ago, I wanted someone to help with the art side of my
webcomic because I had no idea where to start.
I started looking at other people's art in my school until I saw one girl's
drawings and I was absolutely ~amazed~
(SHE'S THE ONEEEEEEEE)
I basically told her: you're my friend now!
She probably didn't realise what she was getting herself into.
We're still friends to this day, but still, I am an annoying friend.
Seriously, this one time at lunch, I randomly asked her
"Will you say fo' shizzle?"
*because she's bllaaaaaaaaaaaccckkkk*
and said "no" *aww*
"What if I get a hundred people to sign a petition?"
"Okay." She said, thinking I wouldn't spend the rest of lunch going to random tables
having then sign a piece of paper and then having everyone in my English and
drama class sign it.
I got a hundred signatures in one day *get on meh level.* and she, being true to
her word, said it and I taped it too. I asked her if I could show the video and she
said no.
"What if I get a hundred people to sig-" "NO." so sorry guys,
here's the audio.
And I'm also friends with this ginger kid and to protect his identity, we'll call
him Nick Jiggly.
That was a nickname I gave him because his real name was Nick Jernigan and
what really sparked our friendship was out love for dating woman *james is a player*. I'm just
kidding, we played 'Magic: The Gathering' and we was (slightly) better than me but
only because he bought the most expensive cards so whenever he would be
beating me,
I would get back at him emotionally by insulting his red hair.
"I attack with my Reaper from the abyss-" SAYS THE GINGER! >:(
he would always laugh about it (but I secretly meant it).
So this one time, my boy scout troop took a trip
to a lake and there was one spot where you go cliff diving and I wasn't on the
young side anymore.
I was more in the middle. And everyone was having a fun time,
swimming and jumping and this one kid named Harris.
(he was one of the young ones) he came up to us and said "My mum told me I can't go
cliff diving" and in my mind, I was thinking
"Mksay harris, YOUR MUM'S NOT HERE." But I didn't really care too much. A couple
hours passed and everyone just started talking on top of the cliff and I spot
Harris sitting by himself and I get an idea. >:)
I said "Hey Harris, why don't you come sit with us?"
(I hope you know where I'm going with this) Harris joined the group,
still it's quiet though and I wanted to push him off the cliff.
I started to think of ways I can get him close to the edge, but the dude was
already standing near the edge back turned probably being of something emotional.
Tell me if you were in my position, you wouldn't push him off the edge and I
scream,
"YOUR MUM'S NOT HERE!" as I push him off.
He was fiiiiineee, I jumped off there plenty of times, we should have seen his face,
he flailed his arms a lot but was dead silent.
He probably thought her was going to die. Hey Harris was a quiet kid, he didn't
have any friends either.
So after I pushed him, people talked to him for like five minutes.
So Harris, if you're watching this, you're welcome :D